"Won't Thanjavur cloud shifting direction
rain over Delhi in new found affection?"
"Won't the rose from Japan
mingle with the Dindigul man?"
"Whichever soil the seed is sown
it flourishes as rice, fully grown"
"Wherever it is planted
seeds take root; taken for granted"
"Life becomes limitless
like the vast sky endless"
"Won't Thanjavur cloud shifting direction
rain over Delhi in new found affection?"
"Won't the rose from Japan
mingle with the Dindigul man?"
"Whichever city re-located
Whatever job allocated"
"Only the thought counts in the end
as pillar of our existence, my friend"
"Life becomes boundless
like the vast sky endless"
[Hindi] Puppy, switch on the lights
Okay, sir
And...wash the vegetables
Yes, sir
Sorry, bro, had to attend
a prayer session with Anki
Er...here's the sweet offered to God
I dropped in at home
That's why I got delayed
[Hindi] Okay, Shiva
Give me 10 minutes
We can start the service now
Puppy
Heat the oil
Not heated oil yet?
This is why I have to come here early
Puppy, what is this?
Highly irresponsible
"When kith & kin, home and hearts align
Time relocates with a destined design"
"Even alone, if faith leads you
the city you go will cradle you anew"
"Though place and
job will rearrange"
"Only the sky above
will never change"
Shiva
- 2 masala dosas
- Okay
- Puppy
- Hey!
How many times to tell you
not to dump it with a bang?
How will we get repeat customers?
The only outlet serving spicy food
If they want they will come
Will they come if you are
glaring and grouchy like this?
You should be jolly
smiling always like me
You hooked me, came to this city
Started this hotel and settled down
You bet you'll be jolly
These 2 years he's the one
slaving behind the stove
Anki, according to my MBA
Half the work gets done
hiring the best worker
Silver tongued as ever!
They have a knack of
walking away half way
"Life becomes limitless
like the vast sky endless"
"Won't Thanjavur cloud shifting direction
rain over Delhi in new found affection?"
"Won't the rose from Japan
mingle with the Dindigul man?"
"Whichever city re-located
Whatever job allocated"
"Only the thought counts in the end
as pillar of our existence, my friend"
"Life becomes limitless
like the vast sky endless"
Indeed!
See you tomorrow
Goodnight
Anki?
[mobile ringing]
What, da? 1 week
since you called me
You haven't come home
for 6 months
Your father keeps cribbing
he hasn't seen you
Ma
If I feel like talking
I will myself call
Why are you getting hyper now?
That's exactly what I mean
It never occurs to you!
Your friend Mani stuck with you
doesn't pick my call either
Okay...okay
Where is appa?
He's here, just got back from duty
- So late?
- Yes
I have to tell you something
Be on the line
Your appa is retiring in
another 6 months
He will get his settlement amount
I'll somehow persuade him
and give you the money
Come back home, da
We can start something right here
Then what about Mani and Ankitha?
Mani has Ankitha, da
Who is there for you?
Why should you suffer
all alone there?
Come back home, da
Okay...we'll discuss all that later
'I have to leave early tomorrow'
I'll call later
You go sleep
Did you ask me to make
idli or dosa for dinner?
I seem to have forgotten
Hahn! Dosa...dosa
I'll make it crisp and hot for you
'Hey! Everyone'
'Come...come'
So welcome to Nahargarh
'Nahar' means tigers
And 'ghar' means residence
Tigers' residence
And this was the hunting residence
For Maharajas
They used to come here,
stay here, rest here
'And then go for
the hunt in that jungle'
And this Nahargarh was built in
'1738'
And it was expanded in 1868
Look around
'See the crack'
'See the name of the couple like you'
But don't write your name, okay?
Shiva, can you help me out here?
Yeah
Okay, bro
Sir, take this
Pass it on
He is Shiva
- Hello...hi
- Yeah?
You have to follow him, okay?
You all have to
follow him, okay? Go
Hey!
STOP!
[Hindi] Stop
Stop!
How can you leave me?
Relax...relax
Okay
- Take this
- Okay
Please come
Come, okay?
Oh-o! Sorry...sorry
Sorry, please click
Take...take
So cute
- Hi
- Um...hi
Seems you are a little late
Yeah, the cab
Oh! By the way
I am Bharadwaj
Sadhana
Oh! Sadh-na
You walk so fast
- Oh! Hi
- Where are you from?
Chennai
Oh! Wow
New to this place?
No, I've been working here for awhile
Oh! By the way I love
Chennai's dosa and sambar
Oh! Thank you
It has such great flavors
Thank you
So what's your plan
after this Heritage walk?
Have you been to Kishangarh
dumping yard?
Um...no
The night sky looks
so beautiful there
- Okay
- And I know a friend who can take us there
Oh! Um...er
Do you know what these rooms are?
These...these rooms?
Yeah, 1 minute
Excuse me
Do you have water?
Can I get some water please?
[Hindi] Hey! Stop...stop
Thank you
Hey hey!
[Tamil] Careful!
I'm oka-
Wait...are you a Tamilian?
Are you okay?
Knowing we are Tamils
you continue to speak Tamil
You are 100% a Tamilian!
'Hello everyone'
'That concludes our Heritage walk'
Travel safe
Have fun
Hope to see you again, bye
Bye
Hey...Sadhana
Sorry, I forgot to get your number
Oh! Um-
- Can I get your # please?
- Yeah, sure
- 874512
- Can you please write it down for me?
Yeah, sure
- Big...big letters
- Okay
Excuse me
Move...move, please
[Hindi] Brother, go...go
Hi
Sadhana
- You are?
- Shiva
Oh!
How come you're in Jaipur?
Same question back to you?
Me...?
Actually I couldn't bear
the nag nag by my parents at home
Forcing me to get married
So I tried to go away to U.S or U.K
Now I've landed in Jaipur
I came running here
to escape from them
[Hindi] Madam, speak in Hindi
I can't understand what you're saying
Brother
My parents
My marriage
So I came away running
Bhaiya, where can I get some food?
- What do you want to eat?
- Good food...where?
- There's a 'dabba' nearby
- Okay
Bhaiya, stop
- 'Thank you, sir'
- Excuse me
You never told me where you work
Anytime you feel like eating
idli, dosa, sambar, visit my hotel
'Tamil Bhavan'
Hey...hey!
Stick to one side, da
Don't keep shaking
What can I do?
That's how they drive in this city
Rising pillion with you!
I'll stop
You prefer to walk?
- Okay...go
- That's better!
Bro
We are visiting an
area called JLN Marg
You'll find many MBAs
and I.T professionals like me
Please keep a cheerful face
Good for our hotel
'I'm curious'
'Who gave you such a huge order?'
I wanted to try out
the food from your hotel
You are delivering it yourself
Aren't you the hotel owner?
Why? Shouldn't the owner
double up as delivery boy?
- I didn't mean it that way
- Hello? Tamilian?
- Yeah
- You know him?
He didn't say a word to me
By the way, I'm Mani, his friend
You asked about
that hotel owner
That's me
OH! Hi, Mani
I'm Sadhana
Nice meeting you
Hi
Bill amount is Rs 5800
You are from Tamil Nadu
After a special discount for you
No need 800
700, that's enough
Aiyaiyo! That's a massive discount
- Thanks a ton
- Thanks
Thank you
Order often
I'll take care of the discount
Give, da
- Bye
- Thanks
Maybe I went overboard on the discount!
This is not your order
All this is M B A!
- 10 - 11
- Forget that
Who is she?
When did you meet her?
Kept it under wraps!
Last week's heritage walk
Tell me wherever you go, dude
I'll come with you
You offer discount
the moment you see a pretty face!
Wait, I'll tell your wife
NO!
Bring it, double quick
I'm starving
Let's see if this is worth
the build up you gave
Doesn't seem to be a big hotel
They are delivering in person
I don't know how this will taste
Forget the food
How is the owner?
Can he be my Mr Right?
[Malayalam] This is simply too good!
No one can beat this
Really yum
- Tell, ma
- What to say?
You didn't say a word
after seeing that boy's photo
Which boy?
- Groom!
- 'I sent you in WhatsApp'
I know you saw
I saw the blue tick
That boy, huh?
No way
Not my kind
Who will be Mr Right for you, di?
If you keep saying 'no' like this
to all the grooms
One day I'll land up right there
with a groom of my choice
Just wait and watch!
You come to Jaipur
I'll go to some other city
It was wrong on my part
to send you to Jaipur
Thanks to your dad pampering you
Aunty, this is Varsha
Pcccht! Ignore her
You choose an apt groom for me
I am ready right now
That's my girl
Such a sweetheart
For sure, I'll find the best
I am ready too, aunty
Will you look for someone like uncle?
Why someone like uncle?
Uncle himself is jobless!
- 'You asked for this!'
- Ma
Office time, ma
I'll call you later, bye
Sambar idli okay?
Hello, ma'am
Your order please
Bhaiya, 1 ghee roast
1 dosa ghee roast
1 sambar idli
Extra sambar
Extra spicy
- Okay
- 1 masala dosa
- 1 corn dosa
- Okay, ma'am
And 1 pizza dosa
- 1 pizza dosa
- Yes
Nothing really, just like that
- Hi Sadhana
- HI
Hotel owner Mani
How are you?
Er...I am-
I am good
Your friends?
Yes, they are my friends
- I am Mani
- I'm Varsha
Varsha?
- Anu
- Anu?
- Deepthi and Shailu
- So nice
- All from our office?
- 'Yes'
[clearing throat]
I'll check if your order is ready
[Malayalam] 'Cheta?'
- Can I get some hot water?
- Malayali?
- Yes
- Okay...okay
'What did boss say?'
What?
What's happening?
I'll tell you later
Go in and tell Shiva
we have a 'bulk order'
What? Another bulk order?
Nothing of that sort
Simply go and tell him
See how he will
come charging out!
[Hindi] No clue what he's saying
Don't know what trouble he's inviting now?
[Malayalam] Add my request also
From today I'm not a North Indian
Malayali!
Shiva, that madcap husband of mine
asked me to tell you we've got a bulk order
I don't know what
bulk order he means
Puppy, take care
Hello
- Hi, we met the other day
- Hi
- I'm Varsha
Food was too good
Everyone wanted to
taste this food again
That's why directly
I brought them over here
- Who is this 'garam masala'?
- I told you, bulk order
- Oh!
- Have you ordered?
Yes, we've ordered
10 minutes
You brought us here?!
Look how he's ignoring us royally
Shiva knows her, huh?
Yes, indeed
Hello!
How's the food?
- Yeah, it's very good
- Simply delicious
You want anything else?
We've ordered so much
Not giving us any complimentary dish?
- Thanks for coming
- Thanks
You should keep coming often
[Malayalam] Anu dear
You should come again
Nice food
Nice ambience
- Thank you
- Feels like home
Thank you
Complimentary
Oh!
Thank you
Hey! Not served
2 masala dosas to that table?
"The more it melts,
feelings only intensify"
"In this instant, poetic lyrics multiply"
"My heart begins its joyful dance"
"My soul breezes into
a love-ly trance"
"Dreams float high
Rise up to the sky"
"Light as a feather
my soul floats; happier"
"In this dream anew
all my dreams come true"
"The floral-breeze caressing your shoulder
now befriends me; bonding us closer"
"As the moments melt, raindrops pour"
"This downpour gets
drenched in the flavor"
"Heartbeats dance within my chest"
"My spirit flies on
a breezy quest"
"Light glows thru' even
the darkest night"
"The noon-day moon
is shining bright"
"A hundred hues blend
to become the sky"
"Unseen wonders celebrate sky-high"
Do you know to cook?
Why will I come here
if I knew to cook?
Oh! Not bad
You actually know to laugh?!
"Within that drifting wave of air
a brand new weather everywhere"
"Like a kite slipping its tether"
"No longer the 'me' I knew, today
Entirely new from yesterday"
"To these roots, water finds its way"
"Down this path, I walked alone
A solitary life, the only one I had known"
"Now our steps match,
a rhythm of our own"
"Like a soft flower,
my days have grown"
"Flavors seven dance on my tongue"
"Away, my burdens have been flung"
"My laughter echoes in joy-fever"
"With a hundred wings I fly higher"
"The more it melts,
feelings only intensify"
"In this instant, poetic lyrics multiply"
"My heart beats to a dancing high"
"My soul blends into the breezy sky"
- Hello?
- 'Hi Shiva'
I'm sorry to call you so late
It's okay
Tell me
I was so busy working
I didn't look at the time
Are you still open?
Yeah, hotel is still open
Er...er
Can you deliver if I order now?
Which hotel does he mean?
Idli okay?
Yeah, quite okay
Okay, I'll come in a while
Okay
Hey! We are closed
There isn't any idli
- Come, da
- Dai!
Anki is all alone at home, da
- Hi
- Sorry, I disturbed you
- That's okay
- No problem
- Come in
Sit down
Your friends aren't at home
'Anu has gone to Chennai'
Varsha has gone partying
with her friends
- Oh! Thanks
- Your dinner
This is the weekend
You haven't gone out?
No such luck
Trying to crack
this code for a long time
Eluding me!
[mobile ringing]
Appa
Shhhh!
- Hello
- 'Hi ma'
- Tell me, pa
- When is Anu returning?
We've made dal powder,
sweet, chips, pickle for you
I think Wednesday
I'll ask her and let you know
But send a small package
How can it be enough?
You aren't coming home anytime soon
No, pa, there's a hotel here
with our kind of food
They serve really yummy food
'Can you be eating
out everytime?'
'They even deliver
the food at our door'
Not just that, dear
We don't know what
kind of oil they use
'Will it be hygienic?'
'Will it agree with you?'
We don't know
Why take that chance?
This is home made stuff
She has garnished it
with so much love
Okay, dad
Okay, I'll talk to Anu
It's very late
Go to sleep, okay?
- Okay
- 'Goodnight, dear'
Hey! What are you doing?
2 minutes
2 minutes for what?
'You are such an
expert at coding, huh?'
Done
Let me see
Oh my God!
Thank you
Thank you!
I don't want your handshake
Part with half your salary, enough
What say?
Take it fully
Last minute deadline
You know how I was tortured
to finish it tonight
Even last week, I had booked
a star gazing experience like this
Of all days, that day
deadly deadline!
I had to cancel my program totally
5k! Gone with the wind!
No refund
Are you so fond of adventures?
Will you be doing
something like this all the time?
I've started only now
I have a long wish list to tick
You know the hot air
balloons in Turkey?
I want to go there
Heard of Ice Hotel in Sweden?
I want to stay there
Try my hand at sky diving
Scuba diving
Road trip by bike to Ladakh
My travel plans stretch
all over the world
But tell me this
Do you know to ride a bike
well enough for a road trip?
I'll be the pillion rider
Wait, 1 second
This is last September
Sikkim trip
- You went alone?
- Yes
[door bell]
I think that's Varsha
- Mani?
- Sadhana
Had dinner?
Done talking to your
heart's content?
It's really late
I have to go
Er...it's okay, dude
I'll wait a bit longer
It will be dawn soon
We can go to the market directly
Buy groceries and veggies
Go straight to the hotel
Hey! Come
Don't forget to have your dinner
Eat, huh?
- Bye
- Bye, Mani
What were you upto
instead of eating?
- Just talking
- Want me to buy your tall story?!
Shiva
- How much longer do I have to walk?
- We are almost there
Shiva
Shiva, where are we?
Wait
You said you missed
the star gazing experience
Surprised?
You can see over there
That's Orion constellation
See that 'L' formation?
Yes
That's called...Coma
Coma Berenices
Oh!
That's the symbol of love
Is that so?
Why?
There's a story behind it
Long long ago, there lived
a queen called Bernice
She prayed for her husband
Ptolemy's safe return from war
She was waiting
Amazed by her love, all the Gods
returned her husband safe and sound to her
That's why it's a symbol of love
Do you really know
about these constellations?
Or are you just spinning
your own yarn?
More or less
I some what know
You are a pro at coding
You show me constellations
You are a damn good chef
Who are you?
I don't know
What flashes in your mind
when you see these stars?
You tell me
What goes on in your head?
If we miss someone very dear to us
Even if distance separates us
That person will also
be seeing the same stars
I'll feel he or she is close to me
What logic!
Won't it be awesome
if we can be like this lifelong?
What happened?
No
No...nothing
No one has gone out of their way
this much for me
I...love you, Shiva
Don't play the fool, Sadhana
Shiva
I was not fooling around
I mean it from the bottom of my heart
When I think of my future
I'll think of only I, me, myself
But now whatever I do
or wherever I go
I feel it will be so good
if you are with me
Whatever I think of
automatically my mind includes you
Sadhana
I don't think this is love
No, Shiva
I know this for sure
You like me too
I like you
You are a good friend
to me, Sadhana
Friend?
That night in my apartment
Is that how you behave with your friend?
It was...at that moment
I got it
You just wanted fun
As soon as I said, love and commitment
you are behaving like a stranger
Sadhana
Love is too big a word
Don't use it so casually
Never expected
I never expected you
to say this casually to me
Then why did you do all this, Shiva?
You brought me here
You told me a story
about Love constellation
When I professed my love
why do you behave so weirdly?
Getting entangled into
all this love, relationship
When it ends in a break up
I can't bear all that pain, Sadhana
I don't have that strength
But our relationship
won't end in a break up
Everyone says this
You came here running away from
marriage and commitment, no?
Then what?
All that...only till I befriended you
Now I feel my life is made
if you are with me
Lifelong
Sounds good as a dialog
But whoever expresses
all these words
Being really happy together
I haven't seen
I thought you are a romantic guy
You are very practical
I...I shouldn't have told you
My fault
Sadhana
Her name
Sahithya
"Before a second fades from view
my love, I am lost inside of you"
"Upon the path you choose to tread
I stretch my soul, by love I am led"
"Your talking-eyes kidnap my soul
Melting in your love, I lose control"
"Mesmerized by your voice I seek
I live within the words you speak"
"Your gaze is like a misty spray
Refreshing my weary heart today"
"Your words become a tidal sway
A sea sweeping my soul away"
"To stay within your gaze, I plead
To be your eyelids is all I need"
"Like a wave, you touch, flow and ebb
I wane away in my own love-web"
"To play with fingers, sweet caresses
I long to share a long path of happiness"
"A hundred stories waiting to be told
I ask for time; our love to unfold"
'Our life was going smooth,
in fact, on oiled wheels'
'Till the matter of career came up'
'Your academic records are very good'
'It's really impressive'
Good, do you have
any questions for us?
Sir
In your Coimbatore branch
Can I get a placement?
Working in Delhi
leaving my girlfriend behind
- I am not interested
- What?!
Sahi...Sahi?
What happened to your phone?
I've been calling you from morning
You are not reachable
How did the placement go?
Got selected?
Did you get selected?
I did
- But I turned it down
- Why?
No, Sahi
I'll apply wherever you get a placement
Only that will work out
Okay, show me your documents
- Give
- I didn't attend the interview, Shiva
I intend pursuing M.S in USA
I had to process my Visa this morning
- That's why I didn't attend your call
- U.S...?!
You never told me anything
about this new plan
It was a sudden plan for me too
I thought I'll let you know
after everything got confirmed
I needed to be with you in the same city
So I declined my job offer in Delhi
You're now telling me this U.S plan
First go and find a way
to retrieve that offer
I would've applied for a job in U.S.A
if you had told me, no?
Be practical, Shiva
How can you be
without considering me, Sahi?
Doesn't look like I feature
in your future plans?
Don't over-think and
assume unnecessarily
She says she wants
to go to USA, ma
She has gone up to applying for a Visa
She didn't utter a single word
to me, you know
She will anyway come back
after studying there
Hey! America is right here, da
Go and see her whenever
you miss her too much
Even I can come with you once
Instead of helping her pack to go to USA
you are sulking with this long a face
Waste boyfriend, cha!
Forget it
Even now it isn't too late
I saw this on TV the other day
To ensure you get the U.S Visa
Visit this temple in Tranquebar
If you go there and pray
forget just USA
You'll get the Visa
for anywhere in the world
"Despite the weather; whatever
will this shared journey stretch forever?"
"Leaning on each other's shoulder
will this love grow stronger?"
"I lose without ever falling down
I look for you daily, all around"
"You and me as 'we' I find
Love, with you my soul is entwined"
"To stay within your gaze, I plead
To be your eyelids is all I need"
"Like a wave, you touch, flow and ebb
I wane away in my own love-web"
"To play with fingers, sweet caresses
I long to share a long path of happiness"
"A hundred stories waiting to be told"
You will get your Visa for sure
First settle down there
I'll come hot on your heels
with an on-site job
What's your plan
after you finish your Masters?
Shall we settle down
in USA...or Ooty?
Hey...why are you so deep in thought?
Shiva, I'm going to Ooty for 10 days
I have to streamline
the factory and workers there
My dad is unable to manage
everything on his own
Is this why you were off-mood
when we were coming back?
Don't over think
Only 10 days
It will fly in the blink of an eye
Yov! Sit down, dude
"Sahi-ye"
Hey...hey...hey!
HEY!
Nothing major, no?
Slight headache
- Let me ride
- Hey...hey!
I warned you not to sing, no?
Lunatic
I'll go meet her
You
Take some rest
Get your bike back in shape
How will I get my bike repaired here?
Hey! Shiva
- Sahi?
- Shiva!
- What are you doing here?
- You are busy 24x7
That's why I wanted to give you
a pleasant surprise in person
- Where are you now?
- Close to your place
Shiva, dad is here
Don't come now
Just go back
We'll meet in Chennai
Ahaaan! No way
I have to see you
I couldn't concentrate at all
on anything, you know
I'm coming
Okay, don't come home
Come to that tree-spot
Sahi
What's up?
Why are you so tense?
You know how these past 10 days
without you was so tough for me?
I don't know how I'll manage
long distance relationship
Let's not be together any longer, Shiva
Let's break up
Hey!
Hey Sahi
Kidding me?
Are you mad at me
for turning up unannounced?
- If you want, I'll go back
- This is tough for me too
But I thought long and hard about us
Let's break up
I can't envisage a future
with the two of us together, Shiva
Sahi
I can't even imagine a future
without the two of us together, Sahi
You don't understand, Shiva
Our view towards love and relationship
is diametrically opposite
For me
I am unable to give you
what you expect in this relationship, Shiva
Sahi, I don't expect anything from you
Small moments we share in our life
Enjoy our closeness
To be with you-
By your side
That's enough for me, Sahi
1000 days since we first met
To me, it is normal, Shiva
You celebrate it in a big way
and you give me a gift
No, Shiva
That-
That's the difference I'm talking about
When you go out of your way for me
I haven't reciprocated
That thought guilts me like hell, Shiva
Sahi...Sahi
Don't overthink and
complicate matters, please
Whatever it is, we can discuss
and sort things out, Sahi
In these 3 years, wherever I turn
I see only you in my life, Shiva
Enough
I was able to realize
only these past 10 days
I was very relaxed
I could think things over patiently
I have to focus a little
on myself now
I...need to plan a little
I need to plan my future
I need...space to do so
[sobbing]
Don't be rash and
impulsive in deciding, Sahi
If you like
If you want we will take a break
But don't say you want
a total break up
Please
I've been in a relationship
for 3 years, Shiva
Even for me this is
very hurtful and painful
But I can't handle this anymore
It's eating my brain!
I can't breathe
Our priorities are totally different
This won't work
Let's stop now right here
I think that's best for both of us
[sobbing]
Don't cry
'Don't cry, Sahi'
If I make you so unhappy
I won't see you hereafter
[sobbing loudly]
It's all in the past now
Move on, Shiva
Anki
He's opening only now
I can't convince you
we'll never break-up, Shiva
But like you suggested
I can't remain as just your friend
And you know that very well
- Sadhana, wait
- Let her go
Hey!
Which one would you prefer for a date?
Red is good
But green suits you better
Pccht! Shut up
I like red
Then why ask me?
Girls, pack your bags
[Malayalam] I'm in a hurry to go
Get up and come
I'm hungry, chechi
Let's go to Tamil Bhavan
Time for some crispy 'dosa'
Don't be so stubborn, dear
Get up and come
No, chechi
You go, I'm not coming
You sure?
Yeah, very sure
I have some more work to be done
[Malayalam] This is
not right, dear, let's go
Your friends have come there
Why didn't you come?
I didn't feel like coming, that's all
Why did you come here?
Will your hotel personally
come and fetch customers to eat?
Hereafter
Whatever you want to think
add me in your thoughts too, okay?
What did you say?
Hereafter, whatever you want to think
Add me in your thoughts too, okay?
Shiva?!
"Kith and kin gathered to celebrate"
"Joys multiplied to escalate"
"Our families unite, near & dear
Million joys echoing cheer"
"Hundred rumors here and there
Loaded with love clearing the air"
"Queen of my heart came swaying
Filled my heart with joy inlaying"
"With her glass bangles tinkling merrily
she electrifies my soul extraordinarily"
"Kith and kin gathered to celebrate
Joys multiplied to escalate"
"Hundred rumors here and there
Loaded with love clearing the air"
"Why did he call her 'wife'?
WIth him through every striFE"
"Why did he call himself 'spouse'?
Makes a home SPecial from hOUSE"
"Together they are
made for each other"
"She is the anchor steady & steadfast
for the wave-length to settle at last"
"Oh my goodness!
This graceful princess"
"She stood before him beaming bright
like many a moon radiating light"
"Our families unite, near & dear
Million joys echoing cheer"
"Hundred rumors here and there
Loaded with love clearing the air"
Do you remember
what's special about today?
What?
Happy anniversary
"A sudden feeling unprecedented
Heart & mind soulfully contented"
"Wonder what you did to me
This blissful bond now in reality"
"You and me should be 'we' truly precious
as vermillion & turmeric blend auspicious"
"A photograph picture perfect
as love and laughter reflect"
"Blessings from the family
to the couple so love-ly"
"She is the anchor, grounded and ready
as the tides in his heart settle & steady"
"Oh my goodness!
This graceful princess"
"She stood before him beaming bright
like many a moon radiating light"
"Our families unite, near & dear
Million joys echoing cheer"
"Hundred rumors here and there
Loaded with love clearing the air"
"Our families unite, near & dear
Million joys echoing cheer"
"Tongues wagging everywhere
Love steps in to clear the air"
'Thank God!'
'He was admitted
in the nick of time'
Don't be scared or worried
We are there for you
He will be perfectly fine
Wait and watch, he will
be discharged very soon
- Sir?
- Yes, doctor
Aren't you the attendant
for the patient in #604?
He doesn't have major external injuries
But because of the concussion
in his head in the accident
There's a blood clot in his brain
That's why he's unconscious
We are trying to increase
the anticoagulants dosage
Let's wait for 3-4 days
If he doesn't regain consciousness
surgery is the last option
Surgery is only 50-50 chance
Even if he survives
There are more chances for him to be
Paralyzed completely
Who is Shiva's attendant?
Patient is conscious now
Heard that, dear?
Come, dear
How are you feeling?
What is your name?
Shiva
Good
Stretch out your hand
Slowly
Any pain or do you feel any difference?
- I'm okay, doctor
- Okay
Shiva...?
You are fine now?
I was petrified
Is my friend alright, doctor?
Just relax
Shiva?
Doctor?
Can you send my family in?
'Sure'
What's wrong with you?
Why aren't you talking to me?
Who are you?
Don't play the fool
- My son
- Shiva
- Maa!
- Came home after so many months
Why should I see you like this?
- Doctor, he will be fine, right?
- He is recovering
Ma, don't cry
I'm fine
You'll be fine, dear
This Mani is the one to blame
for this accident
'Mani?'
Shiva?
Dude?
Are you okay?
Hey!
Why have you tonsured your head?
Tonsured my head?
By the way
How is it nothing happened to you?
What should happen to me?
Ma, just listen to him
He's cleverly covering up his fault
She will come and ask you
You face the music
Hey! Who is that 'she'?
Shiva, what are you blabbering?
Relax, son
Doctor, is he alright?
Hello! Who are you?!
Why are you so concerned?
- Shiva!
- 'What is all this, da?'
Dai!
Where is Sahithya?
Sahithya?
'Relax'
Did you even inform her?
What?
You didn't tell her?
She doesn't know?
Dude, calm down
Not being with me for 10 days
I know she would've missed me
And this had to happen!
It's okay, let it be
If she sees me like this
She won't be able to take it
Doctor
Can I travel in this condition?
My girlfriend will be waiting for me
'Don't worry'
- 'You'll be alright
- Sadhana'
Should all this happen
when she is leaving for USA?
Hey!
Why are you looking at her weirdly?
Sadhana, dude
Just like me she's also
your close friend
Then do you know Sahithya?
By the way, what do you do now?
I run a restaurant
Ankitha and I are married
We run it together
- Ankitha and you?!
- Yes, da
There's a limit to fibbing
You think I'll swallow
any yarn you spin?
Get lost, fibber!
Ankitha and he are a couple it seems
Take a look at this
if you don't believe me
Our wedding photo
Take a closer look
'Dude...?'
- 'What happened, da?
- Shiva!'
- Hey....hey, dude
- Shiva?'
'He is still in shock'
He has lost nearly 6 years
of his memory
Even to process that
will be tough for him
Don't introduce any new information now
And for the time being
It is better if he doesn't know
his girlfriend is no longer in his life
How long do we go
with this charade, doctor?
One day or the other anyway
won't he know the truth as it is?
What if I tell him patiently
all that has happened?
Listen
When you search for a specific item
you don't remember where you've kept
How do you feel?
'I kept it here somewhere'
'How can it be missing?'
This will be our mindset
You'll be so confused
Strain for the brain
This is our reaction
for an ordinary item
He has forgotten his life and
is trying to fix the jigsaw puzzle
If we add a new information
he's unable to process in this crucial time
He'll go into a state of not knowing
the difference between truth and lies
And
It may even lead to schizophrenia
Then what is the solution, doctor?
First to bring that girl
into his life is our best bet
'We need to give him some time
to regain his memories'
'And for now, better to leave him
to be himself and wait'
'Hello?
Sahithya?'
Um...I...am Sadhana
- Shiva's-
- 'Ankitha told me everything'
'I feel bad Shiva is going through this'
'But I can't come over there
the way you expect me to'
No, Sahithya
Doctor feels Shiva has a better chance
of recovery if he meets you
All you have to do is just come here
- We will-
- 'Listen, it isn't as easy as you think'
'Plus I don't want to
go through all of that again'
'So, please'
She cut the call
Really chill, no?
How much more do we have to travel?
- How much further, bro?
- '20 km'
TWENTY?!
Hello?
How many times do I tell you?
Why are you hassling me?
Sahithya, I'm so sorry
Shiva is on his way to meet you
'We are also coming with him'
- 'Please help'
- Why aren't you understanding me at all?
- Please stop him
- I understand your mindset, Sahithya
We told him your dad is unwell
to try and dissuade him from this trip
Now he's coming to meet your dad
My goodness!
First of all my dad
isn't alive now
3 years since he passed away
I'm so sorry
That's not the point
Can you please just deal with this?
Please?
Sadhana, what happened?
What did she say?
She just doesn't want us to come, Mani
It seems her dad died
quite a few years ago
Are you serious?
'How do we manage him now?'
Anki told me Sahithya returned from USA
She is still single and
taking care of her dad's estate
But didn't mention about the dad dying
She is refusing to meet him
He is insisting on meeting her
Okay, let's go, we'll cross
the bridge when we come to it
Aiyaiyo!
Shucks!
Hey...hey...hey!
- Sahi
- Shiva!
'Gone case!'
They are filling my head
with nonsense
It has been 6 years it seems
I don't remember anything
Why didn't you come
to see me even once?
Do you know how often
I tried to talk to you?
Forget it
How is your dad?
Appa passed away, Shiva
What are you saying?
They said he's just unwell
'When Sahi?'
Why didn't you tell me?
Please
When you had your accident
At that time
How did you manage
everything all by yourself?
Okay, forget the past
'Let go, Shiva'
Enough, let go of me, Shiva
Shiva, move
I'm so sorry about uncle, Sahi
I couldn't come
because of this issue
I'm sorry
'Sahi'
I'll stay over here
Is there any lodge nearby?
- Whom is he asking for?
- These two
Hey!
Doesn't matter
All of you can stay here
- Muthu anna
- Yes, madam
- Take their luggage inside
- Okay, madam
- Shall we follow him?
- Okay
- I'll be inside
- Come, da
Thank you so much, Sahithya
I was worried
you may blow our cover
- Sadhana, right?
- Yeah
I told you not to come
and you landed here
We have dealt with
this situation for now
But don't use it to your advantage
I don't want to be part of this drama
Okay
Confirm the deal
I'll sign it tomorrow
'Okay, thank you'
Shiva?
What are you doing here?
Both of them are filling up the gaps
in bits and pieces for me
Only you can tell me
everything about us
You go back to bed now
Let's discuss this in the morning, go
Morning?
I'll spend the night here
First...tell me what happened
- Mani
- Hmm?
- MANI!
- Hmmm?
Not asleep yet?
I'll take care of Shiva
Have a good night's rest
You're taking very good care
He went to Sahithya's room
and shut the door!
Why are you waking me up
instead of knocking at that door?
Grrrr! MANI!
Come with me
Tell me everything
that happened to me
Honestly don't you remember anything?
Tch!
What's your last memory?
Last I remember is
Mani and I were coming
in a bike to meet you
On the way
we had an accident
When I got up
I'm in a hospital
They claim 6 years has sped past
That's all I remember
No sound at all
Maybe they have slept
You go and sleep too
We can talk in the morning
- Why not?
- I have another plan to disturb them
- What?
- I'll tell you
Why are you staring at me?
Nothing is wrong with me
I will be 100% fine
if I am with you
Come, lie down
Okay, tell me this
How long has it been?
What?
Even you forgot?
Come...come
Sorry, Sahithya
I mistook the door bell
for the light switch
What are you doing here?
Hey! I was looking only for you
Such a huge place and unfamiliar
I am scared, dude
What are you up to here?
I came to spend quality time with Sahithya
Ages since we sat and
chatted for no reason, no?
It would have been awesome
if Ankitha were here too
Sadhana
Sadhana, huh?
Shiva says we can chat for a while
Come, sit
Hey! Get up
- Get up
- Aren't we chatting?
Let's go to our room and chat
Sorry, Sahithya
- You said we can chat
- Who asked you to come?
Sorry, Sahithya
We will leave
as soon as we can
You don't get it, Sadhana
You can stay here
as friends as long as you want
Even I want Shiva to get better
But to restart and
rake up my past that's over
He's behaving like we are still in love
I am not for it
Just 1 week, Sahithya, please
You see, if he
If Shiva behaves like this once more
I might have to tell him everything
Don't get me wrong then
No, I'll make sure
you're not pushed into a spot
I'll handle him
Ooty, your beauty!
Mani sir
- Coffee
- Thank you
- Mutha'nna
- Sir
How far does our estate stretch?
How can you ask this?
Our estate extends
as far as your eyes can see
Uncle is calling me
Mani
- Is everything okay?
- All good
Did that girl agree to
have the three of you stay there?
Aiyo, uncle, we somehow managed to do so
Mani, Sadhana taking this course of action
despite the fact we told her not to
I don't know the result or repercussions
What do we do if that boy
doesn't ever remember our girl's existence?
Aunty, don't think that way
It won't turn into a disaster
She left in haste impulsively
- Take care of her
- Sure, I will
'I am banking on you'
Uncle, I'm getting another call
Can I call you later?
'Okay, Mani'
- Bye, uncle
- 'Bye'
- Hello?
- Yes, Anki
Whom are you talking to
early in the morning?
Don't even ask!
Sadhana's parents called me
They are not okay with this one bit
'Even I have serious doubts
of this working out'
He went into Sahithya's room last night
I don't know when
she will chase us out, Anki
Don't lose hope
I know Sahithya inside out
She wasn't in touch
with us all these years
Yes
And still she allowed you
to stay there is a major plus, no?
'It's a little tough to tackle her'
But not impossible
That's true
You're right about her
I managed you well enough
Why should I be scared of her?!
Such a lunatic!
I'm the one tackling you!
With both of you absent
'I am holding fort here
single handed here right?'
Are you pointing your finger at me?
Anki, I love you very much
You know I can't exist without you
Madam, vegetables have been washed
Wait, I'll call you back
Thank God she hung up
She can't sleep if she doesn't yell at me
- Yes, ma
- Mani
Has Shiva woken up?
He got up way ahead of me
Good improvement, he had coffee, showered
and got ready as if he's going to work
I'll give him the meds
after breakfast, what else?
Dai!
Instead of forgetting Sadhana
'If he had forgotten you, my son
would have been with me today, da'
You took him away to Jaipur then
Now this wild goose chase to Ooty
I didn't got so many calls
even when I availed a bank loan!
All of you call me and ask
'Did Shiva eat? Has Shiva slept?'
- Did any of you worry about me?
- 'Okay, forget it'
'How is my dear daughter-in-law?'
Even now you're not concerned about me!
Both your daughters-in-law
are asleep on the same bed!
Sahi...Sahi, wake up
'Sahi'
What? Slept like a baby, huh?
Get ready, quick
Shall we go out today?
Let's go to the lake
You'll feel relaxed too
What do you say?
'Shiva...?'
'Shiva'
He's a royal pain!
Get ready soon
I'll ask for the car
Get ready and come down?
Okay
Sorry
'Shiva?'
- Shiva
- Dai!
What the hell is your problem?
You keep hounding me?
Did you bring me here to be with Sahi
or tag behind you like a pup?
Why won't you accuse me?!
I'm the one answering everyone
Your amma calls me
Sadhana's parents are
so concerned and call me
On top of it Ankitha calls me
I'm curious
Why should Sadhana's parents
be concerned about me?
Um...er...that's-
Why are you ready
so early this morning?
I got up-
Sahithya is awake, right?
I must have 'bed coffee'
with her, that's why
Share coffee in bed, eh?
Move...move
Watch your step, dude
Why was it so late for load
to be dispatched last night?
Won't work get done properly
if I am not there to supervise?
'No, madam, load was delayed
because of load man'
'We dispatched it quickly after that'
Sekar, entry is at 3:15
in the exit register
2 hours late
I've told you many times
not to cheat me like you did my dad
- 'No, madam, just this once'
- Anna
- Stop the car....here
- 'I will ensure it isn't repeated'
Isn't this spot beautiful?
Nothing has changed
Without anyone hanging around
Only you and me
Don't worry, Sahi
Doesn't matter if I don't
get back my lost memory
Tell me why
You are there for me
Hoi!
Why did you stop?
- Hiiii
- Hey!
How did you both land here?
Sadhana hasn't seen Ooty, dude
So I came to show her the lakeside
Didn't you get any other place?
Do you have to come to the same spot?
Why didn't you tell me?
As if you told us and came here!
Why did you both come here?
We just wanted to go
for a long drive and look around
It's been ages, right?
I was wanting to check
if I remember anything?
First proper decision of yours
since we came here
Look around patiently
Sahi, come...come
Sit...sit...sit
This was THE bench!
I lay down on your lap
in this very bench
On her lap?!
Good lord!
I was lying on your lap
and we had a good time
They were simply chatting it seems
Somewhere here
There must be a bridge
Can you see that bridge over there?
'Yes'
That's a very important spot in our life
'Right, Sahi?'
You walked on that bridge
to this lake, huh?
- Doesn't affect me
- No
This side is Emerald lake
- Oh!
- That side, avalanche
Hahn!
In between
Just the two of us
Sitting literally
glued to each other
- Oh!
- It was there
We first
Kissed
Aiyaiyo!
Sun set
Cool breeze
It was just magical
Right, Sahi?
He remembers everything except you
'What did you tell her?'
I was asking her how
you kissed under water?
You are stunned by just this?
Follow me
I'll show you something
'Is that so?'
Come, we can handle it
Sahi
Do you remember?
- It was behind that bush-
- Dai...dai!
- I got it
- Hey!
Dirty mind!
Behind that bush
'A wounded puppy was yelping in pain'
'Sahi and I'
Admitted the pup in a hospital
Then what happened?
After that
That dog recovered
Sired 4 pups
Same way, Sahi and I-
'My fault, dude'
Please stop your recollections
- She is walking away
- Sahi
- Sahi-
- I'll get her
- I'll bring her
- Shiva
Can we go to some place
both of you haven't been to, please?
You know
To get a boyfriend who remembers
all these sentimental stuff
Very rare
A boyfriend who remembers everything?
- You?
- Hahn!
You tell me
How's your boyfriend?
You got one?
Or are you single?
I have
But I don't have
That means?
That means...!
How do I explain?
We are truly in love
But he isn't exactly with me now
Oh! Like 'taking a break'
That kind of love?
That's one way of putting it
Hey! Sorry
I stirred feelings deep down
I think I made you feel
Cha...cha! Not at all
He'll come back to me
You bet he will!
If both of you love truly
Wherever he is
Whatever happens
Your love will unite the two of you
- Really?
- Of course
Take our example
Sahithya and me
We have had so many tiffs
Wherever she is
Whatever happens
I know very well
We will be back to each other
Mani...Mani
- Sahi
- Mani, wait for me
Sahi...Sahi
Okay
Here, Sadhana
- Sahithya?
- No, thanks
Sahi
This seems so new to me
Have we come here?
No
Super, eh?
[Hindi] Bhaiya, give me one more plate
How did I speak Hindi now?
How do I know Hindi?
Are all of you hiding
something from me?
[Hindi] In big, big countries
Such small little things
keep happening
[misquoting the iconic dialog from 'DDLJ']
Heard that?
Even I speak Hindi
This is common
Everyone can speak Hindi
Half the chaat stalls in our country
are run by our 'bhaiyas'
Enjoy the 'pani puri'
We bought 3 plates
Nothing complimentary with this?
'We bought 3 plates'
'Nothing complimentary with this?'
Give me a few
Hey Shiva...Shiva
In such cases, memory flash
is a sign of improvement
He may suffer from headache for awhile
But he'll be alright in a few hours
If we go on like this
will he get back his memory, doctor?
Hahn...he may regain it
in bits and pieces
But we can't predict
the time frame exactly
Maybe you can try to
recreate some scenarios
...which will help trigger his memory
Okay, doctor
As far as possible
Recreate positive, happy moments
Sure, doctor
Thank you
'Dude'
Isn't Sahithya more beautiful
than our college days?
Dude, first of all
did you remember anything?
It came in a whiff
And disappeared
Disappeared, huh?
Okay, da
But did you remember anything?
My head was splitting
Do you feel better now?
Then get up and sit, machan
Controlling myself for a long time
Want to pee
Sahi
I feel like running away somewhere
instead of managing all this single-handed
Sahi, don't say that
This factory, estate
Watching you run them so smoothly
I am so proud of you
What?
Nothing
Why should you struggle
doing all this on your own?
Shall I join you here permanently?
Will you leave everything and come?
You say 'okay'
I'll come here
First you recover fully, okay
'Shivaaa?'
'Shiva...?'
Mutha'nna has made
piping hot cashew fritters
Delicious, enjoy
Sadhana, what did the doctor say?
Doctor
Wants him to take the tablets
and rest up completely
He said no one should keep chatting
and disturb him unnecessarily
He needs deep sleep
Shiva bhaiya
Brother?
"Like a warm cloud vapory
hovering over a stone solitary"
"I saw you, my soul's deepest memory"
"Like a monkey on a stone seated
playfully I somersaulted"
"Thanks to you, I felt accepted"
"O jasmine, blooming on the hill"
"Is your love a stubborn spirit still?"
"Daily stirs confusion contrary"
ANKITHAAA!
"Kindly shower me with mercy
Come, rescue me from my misery"
"The maiden from this tea-estate
nestled in my heart, my soul-mate"
"Slowly, softly, gently
she sprayed love soulfully"
"Lord Vishnu's consort, by divine grace
between heaven & earth I float in a daze"
"Kindly do not ask me
to come down to reality"
"I cast a spell on hamlets within my view
to keep other hearts from going mad too"
"Kindly do not kill me
by an intoxicating spree"
"Garlanding Lord Muruga I pray
I go in circles in a frenzied sway"
"Won't the Lord I trust with all my heart
unite me with my long lost sweetheart?"
"Outpourings of my soul tucked in, I pour
All my love in a string of rosary encore"
"Won't the angel I love with all my heart
reciprocate her feelings; never to part?"
Enough...enough
"Cold winds pierce with a needle's sting
where misty waters ripple as spring"
"Let us spend quality time, you & me
Make magic happen happily"
"In the forest where the tuskers roam
where mountain bees have built a home"
"Let us cuddle and canoodle together
Make a million tiny hearts, now & forever"
"Wild rose in the jungle here"
"Southwest blooms, I’ll gather near
to string a garland for you, my dear"
"Nectar honey within my reach are you
I will keep you happy lifetime through"
"With your tender feet resting
on my lap warm and comforting"
"Like a warm cloud vapory
hovering over a stone solitary"
"I saw you, my soul's deepest memory"
"Like a monkey on a stone seated
playfully I somersaulted"
"Thanks to you, I felt elevated"
"O jasmine, blooming on the hill"
"Is your love a stubborn spirit still?"
"Daily stirs confusion contrary"
"Kindly shower me with mercy
Come, rescue me from my misery"
"The maiden from this tea-estate
nestled in my heart, my soul-mate"
"Slowly, softly, gently
she sprayed love soulfully"
"Lord Vishnu's consort, by divine grace
between heaven & earth I float in a daze"
"Kindly do not ask me
to come down to reality"
"I cast a spell on hamlets within my view
to keep other hearts from going mad too"
"Kindly do not kill me
by an intoxicating spree"
"Garlanding Lord Muruga I pray
I go in circles in a frenzied sway"
"Won't the Lord I trust with all my heart
unite me with my long lost sweetheart?"
"Outpourings of my soul tucked in, I pour
All my love in a string of rosary encore"
"Won't the angel I love with all my heart
reciprocate her feelings; never to part?"
[Hindi] Don't be so worried
- Bhaiya will recover soon, ma'am
- Okay
Guys
Just a few more days
I'll call you back
- Good news for you
- What?
We are engaged
Meaning?
What do you mean?
That means
We are getting married
Wedding bells
Sahithya
What is he blabbering?
Is it true?
Hey!
I thought you'll be happy for me
Instead, you're questioning us?
Congrats!
Shiva and...Sahithya
'Thank you'
- Congrats, dude
- Thanks, machan
- I hope you'll invite me
- How can I get married without you?
- You are my best man
- Informed your family?
Fixed the wedding date?
I have to, come
First let me call my parents
Sadhana?
What is this, Sahithya?
If I say 'no', I know
how he will react
It isn't tough for you
to cut him off from your life
He barged into my estate-
What if he proposes?
Why did you accept the ring?
Do you think I want this?
I'm neck deep in this charade for your sake
Siva has to recover, right?
Have you forgotten that?
Please don't give me this attitude
Oh! Shiva has to recover, no?
Then you take care
and help him recover
Take Shiva and leave, Mani
What happened, Sahi?
He's slowly recovering
and getting back to normalcy
You don't get it, Mani
No matter how much
I ignore him and move away
He follows me like a lost pup
I feel...it's déjà vu
I'm starting to like all this, Mani
I'm saying it because
I don't want to think that way
It's better for all of us
if you leave right away, today
What are you thinking?
I can't stick around
watching him go gaga over her, Mani
If you want, I'll hit him
on his head with a pounding stone
Either he regains his memory
Or his chapter closes, end of story
I have a better idea
Hit her instead
No, Mani
I feel terrible
I don't know if I can
stick around here any longer
You came here well aware
of what's in store
I know I came
with my eyes wide open
But it doesn't look like
he will ever remember his past
Will he remember everything
if you aren't here?
I don't know all that
But he will be happy
prancing around with Sahithya
Sahi
Hey...dai!
Aiyo!
What do you think
when you look at stars now?
If I look at these stars
I think only of you
Is that so?
Do you know this?
When people die
they turn into stars
If I die all of a sudden
I'll turn into a star
and keep looking at you
Say, 'wrong...wrong...wrong'
Say it
'Wrong...wrong...wrong'
You can survive without me
But without you
So I'll die before you
and become a star
Your turn to say
'wrong...wrong...wrong'
What is it, da?
Lie down, dude
'Aiyo!'
Sahi
Where's your ring?
Ring-
Ring is too loose
I didn't want to lose it
So I removed it
Oh! Too big for you?
Yes
First I must re-size it
I'll come with you to the factory today
I'll get to know everything
No, it's okay
You eat patiently
I have a lot of pending work
- I can eat later
- No...no
I can manage
Take your tablets properly
Rest up, okay?
Why does she avoid me like this?
I came all the way
only to be with her
Not smiling at me, not talking to me
Just having a sulky face all the time
You are obsessed 24x7
First try to get your memory back
Instead you keep harping about her
Forever chanting
'Sahi...Sahi...Sahi'
Shiva, she's just a part of your life
She's not your entire life
You are going overboard
You won't understand, Sadhana
Correct
Like you said
She isn't my entire life
But she is the most
important person in my life
She doesn't spend time with me
She doesn't talk to me like she used to
Imagine how I'll feel
Truth be told
I feel like dying
Hey! Why this thought?
Say 'wrong...wrong...wrong'
Say it out loud
'Wrong...wrong...wrong'
Wrong...wrong...wrong
Talking nonsense of dying etc
Hey Mani
I'll ask you something
- Be honest with me
- What?
Between Sadhana and me
Was there anything
Anything?
Was there any link?
What will you do
if I say 'yes' now?
Hey! What are you saying?
Did I cheat on Sahithya?
Thank God
I don't remember anything
First task
Pack her off from here
I must start my life
fresh with Sahithya
But she and I-
'Hey...hey...hey'
I was just joking, da
Will you betray your love?
You can't manage one girl
- On top of it, cheat, huh?
- Lunatic!
Your joke timing is terrible!
So nothing happened, right?
As far as I know, nothing
Okay, but tell me
Why this sudden doubt?
Sahithya is acting weirdly
ever since we arrived
Pcccht!
Something is wrong
But I can't pin it down
Dude, you remember the Sahithya
you knew 6 years ago
She would've changed a lot
in this time frame, da
That's why you feel she is acting weird
Huh?
Whatever may change
Some things will still be the same, no?
Don't go around in circles
in a confused state
Her dad is not alive
You are putting in
your best effort anyway, no?
You are trying
- Mutha'nna
- Tell me, sir
Go to the factory
- Pick up 2 tea packets
- Okay, sir
Come back tomorrow
- Tomorrow?
- Huh?
Okay, sir
'He over thinks and says
one thing after another'
Akka, you can take off today
I'll clean, you can leave
Give it
Why do you look surprised? Go home
[whistling]
- Puppy
- Hahn, bhaiya?
Here, this is for you
Watch a movie
Come back late tonight
What?
Enjoy
Okay
Hey...hey
Give it to me
- 'Yeah'
- Hey!
Where are you off to?
I decided to cook for all of you
You planning to cook?
Why are you looking at me weirdly?
What's that?
Show me
I'll call you back
Cashew, almond, pistachio
Whom is this list intended for?
How many people is this list for?
Like you are cooking
for a hotel bulk order
'Urad dhal
Thoor dhal'
'Basmati rice'
Basmati rice is fine
- Shiva, you okay?
- Shiva!
- Hey dude
- Shiva, what happened?
Dude, nothing to worry
- Shiva
- Come, dude
- What happened?
- Don't worry, dude
Nothing is the matter
You will be fine
Sadhana
Shall I ask you something?
Ask, Shiva
Will you do me a favor?
Go with Mani
Buy the groceries in this list
I just feel like cooking today
- He wants to cook?
- Sadhana, dosa...dosa
He remembers making dosa in Jaipur
Please, Sadhana
Okay, Shiva
We'll get this list for you
- We'll be back
- Thank you
You're okay, right?
We'll be back soon
You take rest
Chances of him remembering
if he cooks, right?
Hot chocolate?
Thank you
Shiva
I couldn't have a heart to heart chat
in front of the two of them
I know you want to talk freely too
But you can't, no?
Tell me now
Did I take good care of you
these past 6 years?
Yeah, Shiva, of course
Will we fight or-
Were we happy?
A bit of both
This and that
Then what happened?
Was I a good boyfriend to you?
What?
No, huh?
Shiva
How someone can love selflessly
I learnt only from you
You've actually been there for me
Stop crying
No...no...no, it's okay
- Nothing
- Why are you feeling sad?
- Shiva
- I won't go anywhere without you
Okay?
Okay...okay
Were you always
Were you always so beautiful?
- Shiva, shut up
- Or did I forget that too?
Bye
- Sahi, wait
- Pcccht! Shiva
Shiva, please
- Shiva
- Sahi
'Sadhana'
Sadh-
Sadhana?
'Sadhana, wait'
Sadhana
Sadhana, wait
1 minute
Hey Sadhana
Sadhana?
Open the door
'Sadhana, let's talk it over
1 minute, open the door'
'Sadhana'
Sadhana
'1 minute, please open the door'
'Sadhana'
Sadhana
Hear me out, Sadhana
- Hey!
- Sadhana
What happened, da?
Her boyfriend ditched her it seems
Sadhana
Sadhana, where are you going?
Hey! What is the matter, da?
She will listen only to you, go
Sadhana
Sadhana, wait
Where are you going?
- Sadhana
- Please don't follow me
Go and continue with her
I'm sorry I disturbed you
I have to go
Sadhana, don't worry
If your love is true
it will make you re-bond
Maybe my love was not true enough!
He has left me
He's no more
That's all
Hey!
- Stop...stop
- What, da?
Stop
Hey Shiva
Hey?
'Let's not be together any longer, Shiva'
'If I make you so unhappy'
'I won't see you hereafter'
Sahi
I'm leaving
Hmmm
I thought I shouldn't relive the pain
of an experience that hurts us
Only today I understood
the intensity of that feeling
When we went through the break-up
I decided I shouldn't hurt you
or disturb your life
But
I came back to you
with my memory erased
I behaved like a madcap, no?
No, Shiva
Thanks a lot, Sahi
Being so patient for my sake
How much you've gone
out of the way for me, Shiva
I am the one who said
all sorts of stuff and hurt you
I'm sorry
It's okay, Sahi
The fact we split up
I think is for the good
I disturbed you too much, right?
I am always alone here
It was nice to have
all of you around
You wait near View Point, Sadhana
We'll come there
We've left
Time's up
I'll leave now
Why haven't you left yet?
I remembered my break-up, Sadhana
For all the drama you enacted
all these days
Thanks
'What do you think
when you look at stars now?'
What?
I asked you, 'what do you think
when you look at stars now?'
What do you think?
Somewhere
I've heard this theory
'When people die
they turn into stars'
'If I die all of a sudden'
'I'll turn into a star
and keep looking at you'
Why are you smiling?
No
You have already told me this
Oh!
Have I told you?
Hmmm
Tell me
What happened to your guy?
Nothing happened
He will come back into
my life definitely
subtitled by rekhs